Tanonaka... We have a guest?
Actually, I'm not quite sure...
He says he wants to
"hear the calls of God".
I've never had much interest
in this mundane world,
which is why I didn't hesitate
to create the envelopes.
But ever since then, He hasn't called to me.
We're here to listen, if you'd like.
Sure, maybe He was the one
who led you here today.
What we heard that day was inconceivable.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
This man named Kou Kirishima claimed
he succeeded in calling spirits
into existence 13 years ago.
He heard God's call and became
His subject, and ever since,
he was connected to His world,
in the domain of the spirits and mind.
And with His guidance,
he created the Mother Light,
the ultra space-time
construction interference device.
He used its powers to collect
the greed of humanity,
enclosed it into envelopes as
"Prime Rights" and "Rights",
and drew them into this world.
But... from the moment I gave the envelopes
to my father, He ceased to call upon me.
In the near future, there will be many
fraudulent gods who possess various powers.
If that incurred the wrath of God...
I want to recover the Rights
and return them to the Mother.
I couldn't comprehend any of it.
You are currently looking
at this screen
But it didn't take long for me to understand.
Seraphiel and I were spared from Tasuketsu
thanks to the Mother's abilities.
And then...
Oh, welcome back.
How was the Camp?
Did you find any resources?
Information on the Rights
was mostly redacted.
But more importantly...
I can't believe it. Teppei
and Haruto were test subjects.
And how is it possible
that Haruto is the Emperor?!
The Emperor died and their Rights
were returned to the Mother, weren't they?!
Then Haruto is already...
Kisaragi-san...
I've made up my mind.
I'll get Haruto and Teppei back!
Even if I have to become the devil himself!
There may be a Right to revive Haruto.
And the Obedience Right
hasn't been returned to the Mother,
which means Teppei is still alive!
If I can just find him, we can use
his Obedience Right to save Haruto!
Then you'll need a priest.
What?
We've been on this journey
together for a long time.
I understand your love for family very well.
When all of this is over,
I'll forgive your sins in the name of God.
And we can celebrate your love
and bless you all.
Then I'll lend you my help, as well.
"Maybe He was the one who led you here."
Remember?
Kou. Tanonaka.
No.
From now on, I'm no longer Tanonaka.
Seraphiel.
For the sake of Kou's wishes, and yours,
I will pray for blessings on you
and forgiveness of your sins
as the "Angel of Prayer".
Seraphiel...
Then from now I'll be...
The Empress... No, the Queen.
The precursor to the Empress, waiting for
the Emperor to abdicate his throne.
I swear to find the two of them!
And save them!
You'll need some faithful servants.
Over a month later,
our efforts finally bear fruit.
Glad you're here, Raion.
We're all gathered then.
Now let's hear where Teppei is... Iruga.
The person we were looking for
was my big brother.
We've been waiting for you
to hear his whereabouts, Raion!
Wow, that's quite the honor.
Ready for the big reveal?
Teppei-chan is...
...at the Emperor's tower.
He already died during Tasuketsu's test run,
and he's become part of the tower itself.
Big bro...
It's all my fault.
Iruga said that Teppei didn't
use the Obedience Right.
Yeah, because he didn't want to endorse
the Camp's actions by using his powers.
So instead, he used it to prevent
forfeiture of the Obedience Right...
sounds like something Teppei would do.
Seraphiel is waiting for us,
ready to celebrate.
Ready, Haruto?
Compound Exercise of the Rights!
"Creator's Command"!
Prime Right of Recovery!
Recover the body of Teppei Yoshii!
Resynthesize!
Teppei!
Big bro!
I'm so sorry.
Let's hurry back to the church
and revive him.
The ultimate blessing is waiting for us!
Meguru.
Yes, milady!
Prime Right of Exchange!
What's the matter?
Milady, I've been transporting by
exchanging places with designated landmarks,
but I'm not able to exercise
exchange with the next landmark.
Because we took the liberty of removing it!
There's been an explosion
at the church's warehouse!
We may have been exposed to their attack.
Seraphiel's taking a look now, so
you might wanna wait for his response.
What's up?
I was just checking the time and...
We've lit the signal fire.
All members attack the Queen's
quarters! Go!
...I saw their message!
We've lit the signal fire.
All members attack the Queen's
quarters! Go!
I knew it was them!
I guess I was right to steal a device
so we could intercept messages
between core members.
Even considering Seraphiel's competence,
leaving him the entire enemy army is risky.
They're based in Tokyo.
If they were to invade the church,
they'd be coming from the south.
Breakup towards the south
and intercept their attacks!
Roger that!
Iruga, be on the lookout for Yagihashi.
Oh boy, you think that highly of me?
That's touching.
Iruga, Ikusa, Meguru, Mutsuki... Off you go!
As you wish!
Yes, milady!
Um, Your Majesty? Does that mean I go too?
Huh? Oh right.
Kai Kasai! Go attack!
I'll go too!
What?!
I may not have powers, but I know them best.
I'm sure I can help.
That'll be a relief!
B-But Raion!
I wanna do what I can for you too, Haruto.
Raion!
Promise me the three of you will stay here.
I don't want anything to happen to you, Haruto.
Yeah... I promise!
All right, let's go Raion!
Yeah!
A suicide mission, huh...
It's a mission with the best chance
to settle this once and for all.
First, we'll lead the Queen to the tower.
Most likely, she'll take the Emperor,
Kou, Meguru, and Ouno.
And Seraphiel will be left home.
Then, Iruga will place Yagihashi's original
bombs near the church and set them off.
Seraphiel will evacuate
the rest of the Queen's servants
and we'll lead them
to a designated location.
Finally, Ouno will show the Queen
a message sent to this device
and she'll order her officers to intercept.
Make sure to separate them
from the Queen, Emperor, and Kou.
And one more thing.
I have something for Ouno and Nihonyanagi.
Huh? Me too?
A parting gift.
Around here should do.
Space division.
I've been ordered to take Pres.
No change in plans for Ikusa
or Meguru, and no new Rights.
Meguru went west, Ikusa went southwest,
Mutsuki went southeast,
and I'm taking the east.
Kai's location will be traced
through Raion's GPS.
And we're all set!
His messages are coming in!
Presentation Right! Simultaneous transmission!
All members attack your target!
As planned, the enemy army has dispersed.
Find the enemy with the
best prospects for your victory.
Bingo.
The hell?
What's this? Marbles?
Endless duplication and maintenance
of the owner's "only remaining" object:
the Prime Right of Obtainment.
I meant to trip you, but I guess I failed.
You think I'm some idiot?!
Hey! Stop right there!
Multiply the gravity within
a ten-meter radius by...
one thousand!
Delete target!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Wha?! You're gonna run?!
Oops, am I too much for your
short, stubby legs to catch up with?
Excuse me?!
I won't let you get away, stupid bitch!
Prime Right of Exchange!
Too bad...
Unlike you, I don't have to worry
about running around all over the place.
Taking off again?!
Knock it off!
According to Knight, the Exchange
Right's range is 30 meters.
Changing locations doesn't necessarily
mean she'll catch up to me.
Where is he hiding?
He can only control gravity
within a certain radius.
I'll be fine as long as I keep my distance.
Still! How can I defeat him
without getting close?!
I better work fast, if I want to stall him!
There!
Dammit! How?!
My ability to listen to others' voices:
the Right of Hearing.
I should have used it sooner.
Multiply gravity by 100 million!
No way!
Prioritize elevation over forward trajectory!
Shoot! I used my power!
It's only a Right. He can
resist it with willpower.
If he caught on to that, I'm in trouble!
He curved the trajectory?!
It must be a Right!
No need to rush...
First, I'll use willpower to see
if it's under the Permission Attribute.
Then I can narrow down
its attribute and abilities.
Here goes nothing.
It's no use running!
See how easy that was?
Don't get too cocky!
I learned how to fight
from Saaya and Hayato!
Don't you dare compare me
to the likes of you!
Hikari?
So she's been hiding this entire time!
She's within my range.
I don't know what you were plotting, but...
Take this!
That's what you get
for betraying us, Hikari!
Rubber?! A fake knife!
The initial blow is key
with the Compliance Right.
The best chance of success
comes down to the first try...
Jump backwards exactly where you stand!
Huh?
I heard you... Over there!
Multiply gravity by 100 million!
I command the distinction between Rights
and Prime Rights and their limitations be...
Destroy
...destroyed!
Prioritize...
...that building as his attack's target!
Willpower has no effect.
Is it under the Transmutation Attribute?
Either way, at this distance there's
no point in changing trajectory.
As soon as I'm within range,
I'll crush him!
What?! It's not working?!
Prioritizing my own physical safety
paid off big time!
Fine, I'll exert my maximum
strength of one trillion!
Here it comes!
This is it!
Change the attack's target to...
Touya Mutsuki!
Multiply gravity by a trillion!
Ultimate Prime Right of Priority
Ultimate Prime Right of Priority!
Miyagawa Sheet Metal Plant
There's no use hiding, four-eyes.
I'll resist until the very end!
What a waste of time.
Damn it!
What the hell is this?!
A messenger bag?
So he's been producing this with his
Obtainment Right, from the second floor.
You took off from the back door?
You're quicker than I imagined.
Looks like you couldn't
produce enough to bury me alive!
I will next time.
You wish!
That "sand" was a mixture of
powdered iron oxide and aluminum...
Exposure to electricity
will light it on fire.
Ikusa will perish in a giant explosion.
It's nothing but a simple chemical reaction.
All I did was pray...
How foolish to point your blade at me.
Then you shall bear it yourself:
the wrath of God.
Prime Right under Production Attribute.
Weather Right!
I'm gonna die!
Fuse!
It's so dark! I can't see a thing!
It's pitch black! I'm scared!
Ryuta, what is this?!
So much for firepower.
We're missing the brains.
It's so dark! I'm scared!
That being said...
Kazuhiko, Knight.
You really willing to risk your life?
You're asking the guy who's
already blown himself up?
You're asking the kid who's
already been killed by Yagihashi?
You're right, my bad.
Destruction Right!
You wouldn't wanna damage
the church, would ya?!
How impudent.
Right of Flight!
Tornado!
You know better than to try that.
You sure about that?!
Prime Right under Production Attribute!
Explosion Right!
Wall of defense!
Gotcha!
Is Knight okay?!
That was some tornado he wound up in...
Microburst!
He used the downdraft to minimize damage!
You gotta be kidding!
Nice, Knight!
Fine, no matter...
As long as you three die, I still win.
Hail Storm!
Kazuhiko! How many blows
you got left in you?!
Probably two!
Great! We could use one right here!
Gotcha!
Prime Right of Explosion!
Microburst!
I knew it wouldn't work!
Just look at how jacked he is!
That's besides the point bro!
I'm back!
Knight, you're okay!
Man, you really are strong!
We've got one shot...
I've also suffered quite a bit of damage...
Shall we wrap this up?
Right of Flight!
I won't be fooled twice!
Back to back! And...
The Destruction Right!
Prime Right of...
Explosion!
I'll block them together!
Microburst!
Use his downdraft defense to accelerate!
Here it goes!
Got him, guys!
The Battlefront
The rest is up to you!